http://www.bridgepix.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
How To Balayage Hair At Home
Essential Requirements And Step By Step Guide for How To Balayage Hair At Home
Fashion color trends spring summer 2016
For Spring/Summer 2016 designers were influenced to create a palette which is very calming.
Achieving Flawless Skin
A lot of people want to have fair and beautiful skin, no wonder why the skin care industry has been very successful in the past recent years
Privacy Policy:Bridge Pix Network ("Bridge Pix Network") operates http://www.bridgepix.com and may operate other websites. It is Bridge Pix Network's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Bridge Pix Network collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Bridge Pix Network's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Bridge Pix Network's visitors use its website. From time to time, Bridge Pix Network may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Bridge Pix Network also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on http://www.bridgepix.com blogs/sites. Bridge Pix Network only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Bridge Pix Network's websites choose to interact with Bridge Pix Network in ways that require Bridge Pix Network to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Bridge Pix Network gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up
at http://www.bridgepix.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Bridge Pix Network are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Bridge Pix Network collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Bridge Pix Network. Bridge Pix Network does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Bridge Pix Network may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Bridge Pix Network may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Bridge Pix Network does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Bridge Pix Network discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Bridge Pix Network's behalf or to provide services available at Bridge Pix Network's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Bridge Pix Network's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Bridge Pix Network will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Bridge Pix Network discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Bridge Pix Network believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Bridge Pix Network, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Bridge Pix Network website and have supplied your email address, Bridge Pix Network may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Bridge Pix Network and our products.
If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Bridge Pix Network takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Bridge Pix Network uses cookies to help Bridge Pix Network identify and track visitors, their usage of Bridge Pix Network website, and their website access preferences. Bridge Pix Network visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Bridge Pix Network's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Bridge Pix Network's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
If Bridge Pix Network, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Bridge Pix Network goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Bridge Pix Network may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Bridge Pix Network and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Bridge Pix Network may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Bridge Pix Network's sole discretion. Bridge Pix Network encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a http://www.bridgepix.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
SocialView PixBridge’s profile on TwitterView JoelCulbreath32’s profile on PinterestPages
Fundamental Face Mask Design Features – COVID 19 Prevention Measures
3 Things to Consider When Buying Swimwear
Top Tips for Buying a Quality Sweater
Facts and Issues Surrounding Bamboos and Bamboo Fabrics
Top Vegan Leather Fabrics
